A New Jersey black bear that walks upright on its two back legs and has become a
social media darling has re -emerged and has been captured on video months after its
last sighting. A New Jersey black bear that walks upright on its two back legs and
has become a social media darling has re -emerged and has been captured on video
months after its last sighting.
A New Jersey black bear that walks upright on its two back legs and has become a
social media darling has re -emerged and has been captured on video months after its
last sighting. The bear, named Pedals, was spotted in the town of In a video posted
to Facebook featuring the bear, it appeared to be in relatively good health and was
moving quickly. The bear, named Pedals, was spotted in the town of Oakridge.
In a video posted to Facebook featuring the bear, it appeared to be in relatively
good health and was moving quickly.
The bear, named Pedals, was spotted in the town of Oakridge.
In a video posted to Facebook featuring the bear, it appeared to be in relatively
good health and was moving quickly.
Pedals apparently has an injured leg or paw that doesn't allow it to comfortably on
all fours, according to experts.
Pedals apparently has an injured leg or paw that doesn't allow it to walk
comfortably on all fours, according to experts.
Lawrence Hajner, spokesman for the State Department of Environmental Protection,
said officials expect the bear to make it through next winter.
Lawrence Hajner, spokesman for the State Department of Protection, said officials
expect the bear to make it through next winter.
Lawrence Hajner, spokesman for the State Department of Environmental Protection,
said officials expect the bear to make it through next winter.
The bear first gained fame after it was spotted wandering around neighborhoods and
was caught on videos that were posted on social media and shown on national
television.